[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [2, 3, 1, 0], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": [""], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "How many strings are there?", "options": [3, 2, 1, 4], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block along the incline?", "options": ["+T\u2081+30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "-T\u2081+30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "-T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p"], "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and Big block", "T\u2081: Tension in pink string"], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the direction of normal reaction on block 1 due to B?", "options": ["N1perpendicular up", "N1perpendicular down"], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "answer": 0, "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Perpendicular Forces: ", "Downward Perpendicular Forces: ", "Forces up the incline: ", "Forces down the incline: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Perpendicular Forces: ", "Downward Perpendicular Forces: ", "Forces up the incline: ", "Forces down the incline: "], "showfcheading": "Red block", "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 up the incline ", "T\u2081 down the incline "], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "showfc": ["Upward Perpendicular Forces: ", "Downward Perpendicular Forces: ", "Forces up the incline: ", "Forces down the incline: "], "showfcheading": ["Red block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block along the incline?", "options": ["+T\u2081+30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "-T\u2081+30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "-T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Perpendicular Forces: N1, ", "Downward Perpendicular Forces: 30cos(45)", "Forces up the incline: T\u2081, ", "Forces down the incline: 30sin(45)"], "showfcheading": "Red block", "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block perpendicular to the incline?", "options": ["+N\u2081+30cos(45)=0", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "-N\u2081+30cos(45)=0", "-N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "showfc": ["N\u2081: Normal between red block and Big block", "T\u2081: Tension in pink string"], "showfcheading": ["Red block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block perpendicular to the incline?", "options": ["+N\u2081+30cos(45)=0", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "-N\u2081+30cos(45)=0", "-N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Perpendicular Forces: N1, ", "Downward Perpendicular Forces: 30cos(45)", "Forces up the incline: T\u2081, ", "Forces down the incline: 30sin(45)"], "showfcheading": "Red block", "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+40+T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "-40+T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "-40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["T\u2081: Tension in pink string"], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": "Yellow block", "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 upwards", "T\u2081 downwards"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "showfc": ["Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": ["Yellow block"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+40+T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "-40+T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "-40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Upward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "showfcheading": "Yellow block", "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081p+a\u2082=0", "+a\u2081p-a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081p+a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081p-a\u2082=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "-a\u2081p+a\u2082=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the pink string?", "options": [5, 4, 2, 3], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2081", "-a\u2081"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": []}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081p+a\u2082=0", "+a\u2081p-a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081p+a\u2082=0", "-a\u2081p-a\u2082=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081p, a\u2082, T\u2081, ", "+T\u2081-30sin(45)=3.0a\u2081p", "+N\u2081-30cos(45)=0", "+40-T\u2081=4.0a\u2082", "-a\u2081p+a\u2082=0"], "showfc": [], "showfcheading": [], "tobeshown": 0}]}]